Mommy...
It's Mommy!
She's here!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm positive.
Hey, I scanned again, and
it's Mommy's player ID!
Her coordinates are above us in the tree!
Kirito!
Wait!
Why are you acting like this, Kirito?
Is this person that important?
Are they worth all this trouble?
Watch out, Kirito!
You're gonna hit the barrier!
Kirito!
No!
Stop it, Kirito! It's impossible!
You can't get any higher from here!
I have to!
Dammit, I have to try!
Mommy!
I'm here, Mommy!
You'll be
with
you.
If you're a miracle, you'll be able
to see The darkness won't be lost.
If you live here, you'll be able to see.
We can't see the light.
We won't see the light.
Even each other, we're not
even aware of the answer.
We keep singing, we keep it.
Why are we standing with you?
I'm not even thinking about it.
I'm a real need Park
If you want to be a little bit,
I'll be able to see you
in the middle of the sky.
I'll be able to see you in the future.
Ah! Mommy!
Mommy!
Yui!
Is that you? Mommy! Mommy! I'm here!
I'm up here!
Where are you?
Yui, I'm up here!
Kirito!
Come on, think.
There's gotta be something I can
drop to let them know I'm here.
Why can't I bust through it?
I used warning mode to contact
her, but I don't know if it worked.
What's that?
A card?
Leafa, do you know what this thing does?
Uh-uh.
I've never seen an item like that before.
I can't access the menu on it.
Let's see.
I got it!
This is a system admin access code!
Really?
Do you think we can access
the GM controls with it?
No.
You need the right console
to access the controls,
and the way to find it is
through the system menu,
but even I can't bring that up.
No one can.
I see.
Although, I doubt something like
this would just fall out of the sky.
I wonder...
Yes!
It's from Mommy!
She must have heard us and dropped it!
Asuna.
Leafa, I got a plan.
I need to know where the gate is
that'll get me inside the world tree.
Well, the gate's in the dome
at the base of the tree, but...
You're not thinking about going in there?
The biggest raiding parties
couldn't even get through.
The whole thing's protected by guardians.
It doesn't matter.
I have to try.
It's okay.
Thank you for everything.
I'll be going on my own from here on.
Kitty-toe.
Should we get going now?
Yeah, sure.
What the hell? Is this an event?
Yui, do you know how to get to the dome?
Yes.
Just go up those stairs and then...
Are you sure about this, Daddy?
I'm only asking because based on
everything we've been told about the gate,
breaking in sounds like it's
going to be really hard.
We don't have any other choice.
Besides, it's not like
we'll die if we fail.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
If I have to spend another second
waiting around doing nothing,
I'm going to lose my mind.
And I know you want to see
Mommy, too, just as bad as I do.
I do.
Thou knowest not the
heights of heaven above.
Test thou seek entry to
the castle of the king?
I'm coming, Asuna.
I'm almost there.
Go then.
Prove thou art worthy of thine wings.
Prove thou art worthy of flight.
Here we go, Yui.
Keep your head down, okay?
Okay.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Get out of my way!
I can do this.
Let's go.
Die!
Die! Die, Team!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Asuna, Asuna, Asuna, Asuna, Asuna!
I'm almost there.
Just a...
a little further...
I...
I died.
I always believed that deep
down, this world was just a game.
Is this my punishment for thinking that?
My strength in the game is a lie.
Nothing more than a bunch
of skills and stats.
I didn't give a damn about
its rules or its limits.
I thought I could do anything.
A game where it's okay to die
shouldn't be that big a deal.
Asuna
Get away!
Stay back!
Get him down!
Get him
down!
Oh, my God.
Kirito...
Kirito!
Thank you, Leafa.
I...
I didn't...
Promise me you won't do that again.
I can do this on my own.
But I don't want to cause
you any more trouble.
Trouble?
But it's not!
I was just...
Hold on. Where are you going?
Wait!
You can't do this alone, Kirito!
Yeah, maybe you're right.
You know I'm right!
Listen! I'm going anyway.
Please. Stop.
Just go back to how you were.
I...
I just...
You mean so much to me.
Leafa.
Sorry.
If I don't get up there, nothing will end.
Nothing will begin.
I have to see her again.
Just once.
I have to see Asuna.
What?
What did you just say?
Her name's Asuna.
She's the one I've been looking for
But then...
Then you're...
Oh my god...
Is that you?
Kazuto?
Sugu?
Sugu-ha?
I can't believe it!
It's not fair! No!
Sugu!
Sugu, it's me.
Go away!
Just go!
Leave me alone!
I want to know what's wrong, Sugu.
I mean, it was kind of
a shock for me, too.
And if you're mad because I'm using
the Nerve Gear again, I'm sorry.
I just...
I didn't have a choice.
You're wrong!
That's not why!
It's not...
I betrayed the feelings I had.
I betrayed the love I felt for you.
When I met Kirito,
I thought finally I could give up on
all these feelings I have for you.
What the hell?
I already had!
I said, but now I'm …
Well, I mean love, but you and me, we're …
No, we're not.
I said, no, we're not!
I know you're not really my
brother and I'm not your sister.
I've known all along, for
the last two years anyway.
That's why you quit Kendo, isn't it?
And why you started avoiding me?
It's because you knew the
whole time, didn't you?
You pushed me away because I'm
not your real sister, didn't you?
You did.
Well, if that's how it is,
why do you care about me now?
I just …
I was so happy you came back from SAO.
I was happy because you were being nice to
me again, just like when we were little.
It felt like you were
finally giving me a chance.
That's what I thought.
But now, if this is how it is, I wish
you'd kept on being a jerk to me!
If you had, I wouldn't have
realized how I felt about you.
I wouldn't have felt sad and
jealous when I found out about her!
And I wouldn't have tried forgetting about
you and falling in love
with Kidito instead!
I'm sorry.
Go on, leave me alone.
It's time for you.
Love is a peace. The hope is always easy.
I'm still a little bit tired.
I'm still a
little bit tired.
I'm still a little bit tired.
I'm still a little bit late.
I'm not a little bit tired.
All of them are so, I'm
still a little bit?.
The end is beginning.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Next time, Bonds.